我不被接纳，孤身一人
I belong in nowhere, solitary
我知道它转瞬即逝
I can see it ever fleeting
每个人都有一个不允许任何人涉足的领域
Everyone has a domain allowing no one
真实的内心，渴望被发现
Accuracy inside, yearned to find
我想我已经理解它了
I thought I had been understandin' it
它埋葬于喧嚣并逐渐凋零
It's buried in noise and withering
爱你所处的生活，过你向往的人生
Love the life you live, live the life you love
All of you have to take
你需全然面对
And everybody else may seem a lil' downward
尽管其他人看起来都有点低落
All of you have to take
你需全然面对
Soon, you will see
很快，你将会领悟
All of you have to take
你需全然面对
And everybody's time may seem a lil' downward
每个人的时间似乎都有点滴落
All of you have to take
你需全然面对
Oh, you will see
哦，你将会领悟
Answers seeked, the conflict, soar
答案被寻找，冲突在加剧
Own Way progress, a long seen world
抛开既往的世界，开拓自己的道路
High end essential I touch, redeem soul
触及至高的本质，拯救灵魂
Through all the silence, a brand new wind blows
穿过所有的沉默，一阵崭新的风吹过